article-niche.com 2013-08-08

# The Article Niche Project | Privacy - Article Niche

Article Niche Project Privacy Policy |   
---|---  
  
* * *  
  
[Last Updated **August 2013** ] 

**The basics of our privacy statement**

The Article Niche Project does not share, sell or rent any personal information such as your name and email addresses to outside third parties.

We will not send you unsolicited e-mail. We will only send e-mails to those who request them through our opt-in process.

We honour all removal requests--you may unsubscribe at any time.

We appreciate you subscribing to our list and using our services. We will not abuse that privilege. The Article Niche Project puts a high priority on list accuracy and quality content. 

**Who receives our emails  
**Only those who subscribe to our services receive our The Article Niche Project Newsletter and email programs. Those who subscribe are sent a confirmation email. To ‘opt-in’ means you have entered your first name and email address and clicked on the ‘submit’ or ‘go’ button. 

**What we e-mail**  
To those who specifically request them, we send the The Article Niche Project newsletter. For maximum control and security, we maintain our e-mail list and distribution system on our own dedicated server.

**Unsubscribing& making changes**  
You may at any time choose to unsubscribe to the The Article Niche Project newsletter. To unsubscribe, click on the bottom link of your newsletter. Your request will be processed immediately. You will be removed from our list and you will not receive future messages from us.

All email list messages contain the information necessary for removal from their appropriate list.

**Why were you sent an email you do not want?**  
There are a few possibilities:

  * You have forgotten that you signed up for a service.
  * We are following up on a service you once requested.
  * Someone signed you up without your permission.

**Spam filtering**  
If you are using spam filtering software, you can enter the following email address into your filtering software's "white list" to ensure you continue to receive The Article Niche Project email messages: editor@visionupdate.net We also monitor all spam filters and manually enter any required validation codes.

**IP address**  
We use your IP address, browser type, domain names, and access times, operating system, country of origin, page views, and users sessions (normally available from most computers with the email address) to help diagnose problems with our servers and to administer our Web site.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer. We do not use cookies at all.

**Security**  
The The Article Niche Project web site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Sensitive data, collected through The Article Niche Project's website is transferred via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) server using only the highest standards of 128 bit encryption.

We have our own **dedicated servers** with daily maintenance and backup. We do not share computing resources with any web sites outside of the The Article Niche Project family of sites.

**Notification of changes**  
The Article Niche Project will occasionally update our Privacy Policy based on users’ feedback. If there are any material changes to how we use your personal information, we will notify you via email and provide you the opportunity to opt-out prior to any substantial change to be taken. However, if you have opted out of all communication from The Article Niche Project, you will not be contacted, nor will your personal information be used in this new manner. The Article Niche Project encourages you to periodically review our privacy policy to be informed of how we are committed to protecting your privacy.

**Legal disclaimer**  
Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on our Web site.

The contents herein are solely the opinions of the The Article Niche Project editors and should not be considered as a form of therapy nor advice. There is no guarantee of validity or accuracy. The Article Niche Project assumes no responsibility for injury. If expert assistance or counselling is needed, services of a competent professional should be sought.

The resources that can be accessed through The Article Niche Project are maintained by The Article Niche Project on a without liability basis. The Article Niche Project is not responsible for the content of any information made available or acquired from or by third parties, including errors by The Article Niche Project in reproducing such information for The Article Niche Project

The Article Niche Project (a) does not make any warranty, express or implied, with respect to the use of the information provided or made available; (b) does not guarantee the accuracy, completeness, usefulness or adequacy of any information accessed via The Article Niche Project; and, (c) is not responsible for any errors or omissions in the information accessed via The Article Niche Project or for the results obtained from the use of such information.

Any specific reference by name, trade name, trademark, or otherwise to any party does not necessarily constitute or imply its endorsement of the use of such information by The Article Niche Project.

**Third-party advertising**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

**The Article Niche Project**  
185 Madison Avenue  
Second Floor  
New York, NY 10016  
United States of America  
212-213-3737
